Guide to the Archives Union File (AUF), Section 5: Boxes 257-319
Archives Union File (AUF), Section 5: Boxes 257-319
- International Union of Mine, Mill, and Smelter Workers, Publication (Box 263, Folder 3)
  - Item 18: Text of Truman letter on copper strike, 1947-1956 (Box 263, Folder 3)
  - Item 19: Matusow's book drew union cash, 1947-1956 (Box 263, Folder 3)
  - Item 20: Anaconda Strike is voted by union, 1947-1956 (Box 263, Folder 3)
  - Item 21: Smelter union hits new low in courts, 1947-1956 (Box 263, Folder 3)
  - Item 22: 14 union officers indicted in plot, 1947-1956 (Box 263, Folder 3)
  - Item 23: Copper injunction pushed as 3 firms bar pactin strike, 1947-1956 (Box 263, Folder 3)
  - Item 24: Injunction plans for copper pushed, 1947-1956 (Box 263, Folder 3)
  - Item 25: Unions absolved on non-Red oaths, 1947-1956 (Box 263, Folder 3)
  - Item 26: Key Canada plants tied to Red unions, 1947-1956 (Box 263, Folder 3)
  - Item 27: Union urged to bar Communist influence, 1947-1956 (Box 263, Folder 3)
  - Item 28: Communists take oath to by-pass labor law, 1947-1956 (Box 263, Folder 3)
  - Item 29: Smelter union revolt against Reds spreading, 1947-1956 (Box 263, Folder 3)
  - Item 30: Two unions condemn expulsion by CIO, 1947-1951 (Box 263, Folder 3)
  - Item 31: Smelter union aide defends red beliefs, 1947-1951 (Box 263, Folder 3)
  - Item 32: Save marginal jobs mine-mil union asks, 1947-1951 (Box 263, Folder 3)
  - Item 33: Quits Communist Party, 1947-1951 (Box 263, Folder 3)
  - Item 34: Smelter Union head suspends revolt leader, 1947-1951 (Box 263, Folder 3)
  - Item 35: 8 Locals vote to leave union over Red issue, 1947-1951 (Box 263, Folder 3)
  - Item 36: Kennecott sifts terms, 1947-1951 (Box 263, Folder 3)
  - Item 37: Copper strike emphasizes impending metal shortage, 1947-1951 (Box 263, Folder 3)
  - Item 38: Truman seeks court aid to settle Copper strike, 1947-1951 (Box 263, Folder 3)
  - Item 39: Smelter workers renominate Clark, Publication (Box 263, Folder 3)
  - Item 40: Copper walkout in Utah settled, Publication (Box 263, Folder 3)
  - Item 41: Clark accuses M'Carran, Publication (Box 263, Folder 3)
  - Item 42: Western Mine union in inquiry, Publication (Box 263, Folder 3)
  - Item 43: NLRB seeks curb on Potash Strikers, Publication (Box 263, Folder 3)
  - Item 44: Smelter union is fined, Publication (Box 263, Folder 3)
  - Item 45: Truman orders writ to break Copper strike, 1951; Publication (Box 263, Folder 3)
  - Item 46: President orders injunction action in Copper walkout, 1951; Publication (Box 263, Folder 3)
  - Item 47: Peril cited in Copper walkouts, 1951; Publication (Box 263, Folder 3)
  - Item 48: Talks open today in Copper strike, 1951; Publication (Box 263, Folder 3)
  - Item 49: Mine union's comeback accented in strike vote, 1951; Publication (Box 263, Folder 3)
  - Item 50: US strives to bar Copper strike today, 1951; Publication (Box 263, Folder 3)
  - Item 51: Action by Court sought to halt Copper Strike, 1951; Publication (Box 263, Folder 3)
  - Item 52: Court action set in Copper strike, 1951; Publication (Box 263, Folder 3)
  - Item 53: Jailed union aide gets court hearing, 1947-1951 (Box 263, Folder 3)
  - Item 54: Copper strike won't affect engravers, 1947-1951 (Box 263, Folder 3)
  - Item 55: Union re-elects aides, 1947-1951 (Box 263, Folder 3)
  - Item 56: Metal union fears crisis in industry, 1947-1951 (Box 263, Folder 3)
  - Item 57: Wage board faces dilemma in Copper, 1947-1951 (Box 263, Folder 3)
  - Item 58: 3 companies balk at Copper accord, 1947-1951 (Box 263, Folder 3)
  - Item 59: Copper strike report ready for President, 1947-1951 (Box 263, Folder 3)
  - Item 60: Copper strikers slow in returning, 1947-1951 (Box 263, Folder 3)
- International Union of Mine, Mill, and Smelter Workers, Publication (Box 263, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: Press Releases, 1951; Publication (Box 263, Folder 4)
  - Item 2: Text of Truman letter on Copper Strike, 1951; Publication (Box 263, Folder 4)
  - Item 3: Truman certifies big copper strike to the wage board, 1951; Publication (Box 263, Folder 4)
  - Item 4: The proceedings in Washington, 1951; Publication (Box 263, Folder 4)
  - Item 5: Copper union bars wage board action, 1951; Publication (Box 263, Folder 4)
  - Item 6: Copper union bars board action by refusing to call off strike, 1951; Publication (Box 263, Folder 4)
  - Item 7: President invokes Taft-Hartley Law in copper walkout, 1951; Publication (Box 263, Folder 4)
- International Union of Mine, Mill, and Smelter Workers, Publication (Box 263, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: Correspondence, Publication (Box 263, Folder 5)
    Author: George Prudham
    Notes: Honorable George Prudham, Minister of Mines and Technical Surveys
  - Item 2: In the matter of the arbitration between Alan Wood Steel Company, Scrub Oak Mine and International Union of Mine, Mill & Smelter Workers, 1949; Publication (Box 263, Folder 5)
  - Item 3: Brass Facts, 1950; Publication (Box 263, Folder 5)
    Notes: Nov. 22, 1950
  - Item 4: Gold vs. Sweat: a drama of struggle, 1935; Publication (Box 263, Folder 5)
  - Item 5: Shop Stewards handbook and union members guide, 1944; Publication (Box 263, Folder 5)
- International Union of Mine, Mill, and Smelter Workers, Publication (Box 263, Folder 6)
  - Item 1: A world at peace; a program for peaceful production., 1953; Publication (Box 263, Folder 6)
  - Item 2: Robert F. Kennedy, Attorney General of the United States, petitioner, v. International Union Mine, Mill and Smelter Workers, respondent., 1961; Publication (Box 263, Folder 6)
- International Union of Mine, Mill, and Smelter Workers, Publication (Box 263, Folder 7)
  - Item 1: Report to President Philip Murray, CIO by Committee appointed to investigate breach within the International Union of Mine, Mill and Smelter Workers, 1947; Publication (Box 263, Folder 7)
  - Item 2: A trip through the office of the secretary-treasurer: [checks and balances], 1944; Publication (Box 263, Folder 7)
    Author: James J. Leary
  - Item 3: flyer from the 50th Convention at the Davenport Hotel, Spokane, Washington, 1955; Publication (Box 263, Folder 7)
  - Item 4: The Mine Mill conspiracy case, 1959; Publication (Box 263, Folder 7)
    Author: Sidney Lens; Norman Thomas
  - Item 5: Report of the Fact Finding Committee established by the International Union of Mine to investigate Allistair Stewart's attack on the union, 1959; Publication (Box 263, Folder 7)
  - Item 6: Butte Contract bonus system, 1954; Publication (Box 263, Folder 7)
  - Item 7: When you vote for Mine-Mill, Publication (Box 263, Folder 7)
  - Item 8: Memo, Publication (Box 263, Folder 7)
  - Item 9: Mine-Mill/Bargaining Bulletin, 1951; Publication (Box 263, Folder 7)
    Notes: June 8, 1951; May 25, 1951; Oct. 22, 1951; July 6, 1951
  - Item 10: Facts & Figures - Mine-Mill, 1952; Publication (Box 263, Folder 7)
  - Item 11: Mine-Mill's 1956 Demands, Publication (Box 263, Folder 7)
- International Union of Mine, Mill, and Smelter Workers, Publication (Box 263, Folder 8)
  - Item 1: Resolutions submitted to 47th Convention, 1951; Publication (Box 263, Folder 8)
  - Item 2: Resolutions submitted to 50th Convention, 1955; Publication (Box 263, Folder 8)
  - Item 3: Report to the Fiftieth convention., 1955; Publication (Box 263, Folder 8)
  - Item 4: Jimmy Higgins' handbook: a manual for Shop Stewards, 1943; Publication (Box 263, Folder 8)
    Author: Jimmy Higgins
- International Union of Mine, Mill, and Smelter Workers, Publication (Box 263, Folder 9)
  - Item 1: Mine Mill Research Review, 1961; Publication (Box 263, Folder 9)
    Notes: vol. 2, no.3- 4
  - Item 2: Mine Mill Research Report, 1958; Publication (Box 263, Folder 9)
    Notes: vol. 1, no.1- 10
  - Item 3: Mine Mill Research Report, 1959; Publication (Box 263, Folder 9)
    Notes: vol. 2, no. 1-9, 10
  - Item 4: Mine Mill Research Report, 1960; Publication (Box 263, Folder 9)
    Notes: vol. 3, no.1
  - Item 5: Mine Mill Research Dept. - Lead-Zinc Bulletin, 1950-1957 (Box 263, Folder 9)
    Notes: no. 2, 7
  - Item 6: Mine Mill Research Dept. - Copper-Brass Bulletin, 1951-1952 (Box 263, Folder 9)
    Notes: vol. 2, no. 1-3; no. 8- 9
  - Item 7: Economic issues in 1959 bargaining, Publication (Box 263, Folder 9)
  - Item 8: Facts for bargaining 1967, Publication (Box 263, Folder 9)
- United Mine Workers of America (UMWA), Publication (Box 264, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: The Struggle in Colorado for industrial freedom, 1914-1915 (Box 264, Folder 1)
    Notes: Bulletin no. 1-4 (Series II); Bulletin no.11-15
  - Item 2: State of the Union address by Arnold Miller, Pres. United Mine Workers of America, 1973; Publication (Box 264, Folder 1)
    Author: Arnold Miller
  - Item 3: Statement of the strike situation in Colorado, 1914; Publication (Box 264, Folder 1)
  - Item 4: Resolutions adopted by the Ancient and Accepted Scottish Rite of Freemasonry, 1914; Publication (Box 264, Folder 1)
  - Item 5: Ludlow - being the report of the Special Board of Officers appointed by the Governor of Colorado, 1914; Publication (Box 264, Folder 1)
  - Item 6: The Mine Mill conspiracy case, 1959; Publication (Box 264, Folder 1)
  - Item 7: Facts concerning the struggle in Colorado for industrial freedom. Series 1., 1914; Publication (Box 264, Folder 1)
  - Item 8: The power and authority of the governor and militia in domestic disturbances, 1914; Publication (Box 264, Folder 1)
    Author: Henry Johnson Hersey
  - Item 9: The Colorado mine war, 1914; Publication (Box 264, Folder 1)
    Author: A. A. Berle
  - Item 10: The Military occupation of the Coal Strike Zone of Colorado by the Colorado National Guard, 1913-1914: report of the Commanding General to the Governor for the use of the Congressional Committee, Publication (Box 264, Folder 1)
- United Mine Workers of America (UMWA), Publication (Box 264, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: Statement of the strike situation in Colorado, 1914; Publication (Box 264, Folder 2)
  - Item 2: Read the grievances of the Colorado Coal Miners. Read the Personal Experiences of the Coal miners in Colorado, related by themselves in the Coal Miners' convention held at Trinidad, Sept. 15- 16, 1913, Publication (Box 264, Folder 2)
  - Item 3: An answer to "The report of the Commanding General to the Governor for the use of the Congressional Committee on the Military occupation of the Coal Strike Zone by the Colorado National Guard, 1913-1914", Publication (Box 264, Folder 2)
- United Mine Workers of America (UMWA), Publication (Box 264, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: Address of United States Senator John W. Kern, 1914; Publication (Box 264, Folder 3)
    Author: John W. Kern
  - Item 2: Addresses of Charles H. Moyer, John H. Walker, and President John P. White and Guy Miller, 1914; Publication (Box 264, Folder 3)
    Author: Charles H. Moyer; John H. Walker: John P. White; Guy Miller
  - Item 3: Statement by UMWA President Arnold Millerat the opening of 1974 Coal Contract Negotiation, Publication (Box 264, Folder 3)
  - Item 4: Statement by United Mine Workers Pres. Arnold Miller for release 2 p.m., Oct. 10, 1974, Publication (Box 264, Folder 3)
  - Item 5: Radio address of John L. Lewis, Publication (Box 264, Folder 3)
    Author: John L. Lewis
  - Item 6: Press Release, 1936; Publication (Box 264, Folder 3)
  - Item 7: UMWA Collective Bargaining Committee, recommendations for improvement of the National Bituminous Coal Wage Agreement, 1974; Publication (Box 264, Folder 3)
- United Mine Workers of America (UMWA), Publication (Box 264, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: Save the union (an open letter), 1926; Publication (Box 264, Folder 4)
    Author: John Brophy
  - Item 2: Answer to enemies of 'Save the Union" program, 1926; Publication (Box 264, Folder 4)
  - Item 3: Correspondence, 1926; Publication (Box 264, Folder 4)
  - Item 4: National bituminous coal wage agreement of 1950, Publication (Box 264, Folder 4)
  - Item 5: Facts! An address delivered before the Public Ownership League, 1921; Publication (Box 264, Folder 4)
- United Mine Workers of America (UMWA), Publication (Box 264, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: Arbitration award, in the matter of the Solvay Process Div., 1953; Publication (Box 264, Folder 5)
- United Mine Workers of America (UMWA), Publication (Box 265, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: Before the United States Anthracite Coal CommissionThe relations between wages and production, costs, prices, and profits in the Anthracite Mining Industry, 1920; Publication (Box 265, Folder 1)
  - Item 2: United Mine Workers v. Gibbs - Supreme Court of the United StatesMr. Justice Brennan delivered the opinion of the Court, 1966; Publication (Box 265, Folder 1)
  - Item 3: United Mine Workers of America, Petitioner, v. James M. Pennington et al. no. 48, 1965; Publication (Box 265, Folder 1)
    Author: James M. Pennington
- United Mine Workers of America (UMWA), Publication (Box 265, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: Correspondence, 1948; Publication (Box 265, Folder 2)
  - Item 2: In the District Court of the United States for the District of ColumbiaCivil Action no. 1651-48, 1948; Publication (Box 265, Folder 2)
  - Item 3: In the District Court of the United States for the District of ColumbiaCivil Action no. 1379-48, 1948; Publication (Box 265, Folder 2)
  - Item 4: Nos. 2393, 2394, 2395, 2396 in the Supreme Court of Appeals of West Virginia, Publication (Box 265, Folder 2)
- United Mine Workers of America (UMWA), Publication (Box 265, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: The government of coal, 1921; Publication (Box 265, Folder 3)
  - Item 2: Some aspects of unemployment insurance., 1924; Publication (Box 265, Folder 3)
  - Item 3: John Brophy appeals to International Executive Board for honesty and a square deal, 1927; Publication (Box 265, Folder 3)
  - Item 4: Correspondence, 1926; Publication (Box 265, Folder 3)
    Author: Powers Hapgood
- United Mine Workers of America (UMWA), Publication (Box 265, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: Decision of the Supreme Court of Kansas. The state, ex rel. Richard J. Hopkins, as attorney-general, et al., appellee, vs. Alexander Howat et al., appellants. Appeal from Crawford County, affirmed. Decided June 11, 1921., Publication (Box 265, Folder 4)
  - Item 2: In the Supreme Court of the United States, October Term, 1949. No. 168. International Union, United Mine Workers of America, and John L. Lewis, as President, International Union, United Mine Workers of America, Petitioners, vs. The United States of Americ, Publication (Box 265, Folder 4)
  - Item 3: Supreme Court of the United States, October Term, 1949. No. 168. International Union, United Mine Workers of America, and John L. Lewis, as President, International Union, United Mine Workers of America, Petitioners, vs. The United States of America. No., Publication (Box 265, Folder 4)
  - Item 4: In the Supreme Court of the United States, October Term, 1949. No. 168 and 169. International Union, United Mine Workers of America, and John L. Lewis, as President, International Union, United Mine Workers of America, Petitioners, v. The United States o, Publication (Box 265, Folder 4)
  - Item 5: In the United States District Court for the Western District of Virginia at Abingdon: Jewell Ridge Coal Corporation, Plaintiff v. Local No. 6167, United Mine Workers of America, et. al., Defendants, Civil Action No. 73: Reply brief for the Plaintiff, Publication (Box 265, Folder 4)
  - Item 6: United States Court of Appeals for the District of Columbia Circuit, No. 9943, International Union, United Mine Workers of America, and John L. Lewis, as President, International Union, United Mine Workers of America, Appellants, v. United States of Amer, Publication (Box 265, Folder 4)
  - Item 7: United States Court of Appeals for the District of Columbia Circuit, No. 9943, International Union, United Mine Workers of America, and John L. Lewis, as President, International Union, United Mine Workers of America, Appellants, v. United States of Amer, Publication (Box 265, Folder 4)
- United Mine Workers of America (UMWA), Publication (Box 265, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: Press Release - In the District Court of the United States for the District of Columbia - Ezra Van Horn, John L. Lewis, United Mine Workers of America, H. Styles Bridges (Civil Action no. 1651- 48), 1948; Publication (Box 265, Folder 5)
    Author: Ezra Van Horn; John L. Lewis; H. Styles Bridges
  - Item 2: In the District Court of the United States for the District of Columbia - Eugene A. Curry v. International Union, United Mine Workers of America., 1948; Publication (Box 265, Folder 5)
    Author: Eugene A. Curry
  - Item 3: United States of America Before the National Labor Relations Board, Fifth Region - In the matter of International Union, United Mine Workers of America and Jones & Laughlin Steel Corporation (Case No. 5-CB-14), 1949; Publication (Box 265, Folder 5)
  - Item 4: The case of the anthracite coal mine workers; opening statement and closing argument of Philip Murray, vice-president, the United Mine Workers of America, before the United States Anthracite Coal, 1920; Publication (Box 265, Folder 5)
  - Item 5: Why the miners' program?, 1921; Publication (Box 265, Folder 5)
  - Item 6: Before the United States Anthracite Coal Commission. Employees exhibit number ...: occupation hazard of Anthracite Miners, 1920; Publication (Box 265, Folder 5)
- United Mine Workers of America (UMWA), Publication (Box 265, Folder 6)
  - Item 1: Report of Christ J. Golden, President of District No. 9, U.M.W. of A.: to the Twentieth Consecutive and Third Biennial Convention at Shamokin, Penna., Dec. 19th, 1922, Publication (Box 265, Folder 6)
    Author: Christ J. Golden
  - Item 2: Report of Secretary-Treasurer Thos. R. Davis to the Twenty-fourth Successive Constitutional and Seventh Biennial Convention of District No. 9, U.M.W. of A. held at Ashland, Pa., 1930; Publication (Box 265, Folder 6)
    Author: Thomas R. Davis
- United Mine Workers of America (UMWA), Publication (Box 265, Folder 7)
  - Item 1: Report of John H. Walker, President, District Number Twelve, United Mine Workers of America: Twenty-Fourth Annual Convention, February, 1913, Publication (Box 265, Folder 7)
    Author: John H. Walker
  - Item 2: Third quarterly report of Duncan McDonald Secretary-Treasurer of District Twelve, United Mine Workers of America for months of August-September-October, 1916, Publication (Box 265, Folder 7)
    Author: Duncan McDonald
  - Item 3: Proceedings of the twenty-fifth annual convention of District No. 12, United Mine Workers of America, Peoria, Ill., 1914, ninth day, March 6, 1914, morning session, Publication (Box 265, Folder 7)
  - Item 4: Joint Conference of the Illinois Coap Operators Association, the Coal Operators Association of the Fifth and Ninth Districts of Illinois, the Central Illinois Coal Operators Association and the United Mine Workers of America, District no. 12, Chicago, Ill, 1916; Publication (Box 265, Folder 7)
  - Item 5: Report of Frank Farrington, President, District Number Twelve, United Mine Workers of America: Twenty-Ninth Consecutive and Fourth Biennial Convention, Peoria, November 8, 1921, Publication (Box 265, Folder 7)
    Author: Frank Farrington
- United Mine Workers of America (UMWA), Publication (Box 266, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: The Struggle in Colorado for industrial freedom, 1914; Publication (Box 266, Folder 1)
    Notes: Bulletin no. 1,3-4,6-14; Bulletin no. 1-3 (Series II)
  - Item 2: Militarism: what it costs the taxpayers. Colorado squanders $685,000.00 in six months to "protect" property in two counties on which it receives yearly state tax of $3,560.22., 1914; Publication (Box 266, Folder 1)
  - Item 3: An answer to "The report of the Commanding General to the Governor for the use of the Congressional Committee on the Military occupation of the Coal Strike Zone by the Colorado National Guard, 1913-1914" (Box 266, Folder 1)
  - Item 4: Report on the Colorado strike investigation made under House resolution 387, Sixty-third Congress, third session ..., 1915; Publication (Box 266, Folder 1)
  - Item 5: The Military occupation of the Coal Strike Zone of Colorado by the Colorado National Guard, 1913-1914: report of the Commanding General to the Governor for the use of the Congressional Committee, Publication (Box 266, Folder 1)
  - Item 6: A Fight for industrial justice!, Publication (Box 266, Folder 1)
- American Civil Liberties Union (ACLU), Publication (Box 266, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: War map of West Virginia, 1923; Publication (Box 266, Folder 2)
- United Mine Workers of America (UMWA), Publication (Box 266, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: A message to Taxi Drivers from the Taxi Workers Organizing Committee, 1948; Publication (Box 266, Folder 3)
  - Item 2: Taxi Drivers Meeting, 1948; Publication (Box 266, Folder 3)
  - Item 3: In consideration of the Boston Consolidated Gas Company putting into effect an increase of, 1946; Publication (Box 266, Folder 3)
  - Item 4: Rules of District 50, 1956; Publication (Box 266, Folder 3)
  - Item 5: Report of Officers of District 50, United Mine Workers of America to the delegates of the Fourth Consecutive Convention, Friday, September 8, 1944, Cincinnati, Ohio, Publication (Box 266, Folder 3)
  - Item 6: Grievance machinery and how to make it work, 1939; Publication (Box 266, Folder 3)
    Author: Roy Lancaster; Samuel Machlis; Louis Weiner
- United Mine Workers of America (UMWA), Publication (Box 266, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: Grievance machinery and how to make it work, Publication (Box 266, Folder 4)
  - Item 2: Welfare Plan for members of District 50.(Confidential, for Regional Directors only), Publication (Box 266, Folder 4)
  - Item 3: Important! Do you want to save yourself $48.00 and more?, Publication (Box 266, Folder 4)
  - Item 4: Awaken Railroad workers, Publication (Box 266, Folder 4)
  - Item 5: Railroad workers here are the facts!, Publication (Box 266, Folder 4)
- United Mine Workers of America (UMWA), Publication (Box 266, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: Employee's job evaluation manual, 1952; Publication (Box 266, Folder 5)
  - Item 2: Correspondence, 1929; Publication (Box 266, Folder 5)
  - Item 3: Statement of financial relationship of United Mine Workers of America and Congress of Industrial Organizations, 1942; Publication (Box 266, Folder 5)
- United Mine Workers of America (UMWA), Publication (Box 266, Folder 6)
  - Item 1: Joint Conference of Bituminous Coal Operations and Coal Miners of the Central Compative Field held at New York beginning January 18th, 1923, Publication (Box 266, Folder 6)
  - Item 2: Minutes of joint conferences of coal operators' and coal miners' representatives from Western Pennsylvania, Ohio, Indiana and Illinois, Cleveland, Ohio, August 7-15, 1922., Publication (Box 266, Folder 6)
- United Mine Workers of America (UMWA), Publication (Box 266, Folder 7)
  - Item 1: A brief history of the United Mine Workers of America, Publication (Box 266, Folder 7)
    Author: Justin McCarthy
  - Item 2: Bloody Harlan: the story of four miners serving life for daring to organize a union, daring to strike, daring to picket. Facts from the court records in the Harlan frame-up trials, 1937; Publication (Box 266, Folder 7)
- United Mine Workers of America (UMWA), Publication (Box 266, Folder 8)
  - Item 1: Official notice of election and ballot, 1950; Publication (Box 266, Folder 8)
  - Item 2: Statement of Thomas Kennedyto the Committee on Education and Labor, House of Representatives, 1953; Publication (Box 266, Folder 8)
    Author: Thomas Kennedy
    Notes: mimeographed copy
  - Item 3: transcript - Return American business and labor to the bargaining table - statement of John L. Lewis, 1953; Publication (Box 266, Folder 8)
  - Item 4: transcript - Statement of Thomas Kennedy before the House Committee on Public Works, February-March-April, 1951, Publication (Box 266, Folder 8)
- United Mine Workers of America (UMWA), Publication (Box 266, Folder 9)